The story of a man who took the law into his own finger!
Support Your Local Gunfighter is a comedy,
western film directed by Burt Kennedy.
A con artist arrives in a mining town controlled by two competing companies.
Both companies think he's a famous gunfighter and try to
hire him to drive the other out of town.
Latigo, played by James Garner.
Patience, played by Suzanne Pleshette.
Jug May, played by Jack Elam.
Taylor, played by Harry Morgan.
Jenny, played by Joan Blondell.
Goldie, played by Marie Windsor.
Support Your Local Gunfighter is a 1971 American comic Western film directed by
Burt Kennedy and starring James Garner and Suzanne Pleshette.
The screenplay was originally written by James Edward Grant, who died in
1966; Kennedy rewrote it but let Grant keep sole credit.
The picture shares many cast and crew members and plot elements
with the earlier Support Your Local Sheriff!
but is not a sequel.
The supporting cast features Jack Elam, Harry Morgan, John Dehner,
Marie Windsor, Dub Taylor, Joan Blondell and Ellen Corby.
Garner later wrote that the film was, "not as good
as Support Your Local Sheriff".
The tone is lighthearted.